Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
Where's my husband?
Is he here?
Is he coming?
I get to my spot.
He's not there.
I'm looking around. being like.
are you hiding somewhere?
Like. is this going to be like.
this funny joke
that you make? "Surprise!"
Then I started thinking. like.
is he going to come on a horse
or something?
(DISTANT NEIGHS)
And if he was. cool. like.
I would have been like. OK.
do you ride horses or like. are
you Prince Charming on a steed?
But he's nowhere to be seen.
Do you know where he is?
Seems like
he's taken forever.
Can we get the driver
to hit the roads a bit...
a bit faster?
I just want to get there.
Yeah. the wife could
be at the alter.
You stand at the altar.
The bride walks down the aisle.
OK.
Yeah. I'm just actually trying to
find out what's happening. Sorry.
Hopefully we'll find out soon.
OK.
I'm thinking to myself.
'OK. well. this guy's
obviously not coming.'
I've been standing here
awkwardly for ages.
and I don't want to be waiting
for my husband at the aisle.
Nobody. I don't think
anybody would want that.
Yeah. Hurry up.
Quick.
Ah. this is just too much.
This is just too much.
Oh. I knew she was
gonna be there.
I'm coming in late.
Everyone's looking at me.
I saw her at the altar.
looking up at me.
Oh my god.
It was like. ooh. this isn't
typically how things
are supposed to go.
Pretty sure the guy is supposed
to be waiting for her.
Sorry I'm late. everyone.
How you going?
Hi. how you going? I'm Mel.
Luke. Sorry I'm late.
Where were you?
I forgot the rings.
For the first day of marriage.
you're a little bit disorganised.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I was late.
Do you have them now?
I do. I do. I do have them now.
Do I get 'em out?
No. Not yet.
Um...
I was ready. like. hours ago.
Where's Mum and Dad?
I was ready hours ago.
That's my mum.
This is such a big
event in someone's life.
Like. how do you mess it up
like that?
This isn't just like.
'Oh. I'm sorry I was late
to your birthday dinner.'
This is such a big day.
I've been thinking
about it for months.
That experience for me.
I feel like was a bit ruined.
You look really good.
by the way.
Thanks. But at the same time.
I came into this experiment
wanting to give it my all.
Wanting to find my person.
How's your morning been?
Better than yours. actually.
I didn't forget anything.
So I'm going to
give it a chance.
Family and friends.
today we celebrate
the wedding of Mel and Luke.
All right. Mel.
your wedding vows.
Hello. husband.
I need a man to be the blue
to my pink.
Being blue is making a place
feeling steady. strong and safe.
Being pink is making a space
feel warm. open and loved.
I want a man who will build
all the furniture that I pick out.
And carry all the heavy bags.
while still finding a way
to hold my hand.
(LUKE CHEWING)
When I was doing my vows.
he was chewing gum.
sort of with his mouth open.
I could hear it.
It's sort of. you know.
one thing after another.
I'm searching for
something real.
Someone that makes my life feel
like a fairy tale
and making life feel like
a rom-com movie.
I want to feel like a main
character in this movie
and to feel all the butterflies.
And I'm so excited to see
where this fairy tale takes us.
Love it!
(APPLAUSE)
I noticed about Mel's vows
that she was very specific.
which I really liked.
She was talking about the whole
pink and blue thing and like.
I find that stuff really cute.
She's a bit of a girly girl.
so I'm sure she is quite
traditional in that regard.
Um. so it probably would have
been even more important
for me to be there before.
before she was.
My favourite colour is blue.
by the way.
So I feel like I've got
a little bit of work to do.
Yeah. I do.
And Luke.
Sure.
OK.
Just swallow it.
Like. spat it out
and gave it to his sister.
I actually feel sick
in my stomach.
Just swallow it
like everybody else.
Oh. the poor guy.
I mean. he had a lot
going on this morning.
We're always going to fend
for our brother.
I think it comes down to just
the stress and the nerves.
But I think he definitely
has some making up to do.
Hi. Mel.
I don't know about you.
but I'm pinching myself
that the day has finally arrived.
Sometimes the best chapters
in life begin on the pages
you never plan to write.
I would say I'm someone
who gives anything a shot.
And I'm also the man to get
the spiders out of the house
before you even see them.
I'm also quite handy. I can
fix almost anything you break.
Carry the heavy groceries
and cook you a killer
chilli garlic prawn linguine.
I hope you like seafood.
All I could think about
in the back of my head
was that I didn't feel chemistry
or anything like that.
unfortunately.
Growing up with sisters.
I've watched my fair share
of chick flicks and rom-coms.
He doesn't make me feel
that pink feeling
that I wanted to feel.
I'd be lying if I said
I didn't want that happy
fairy tale ending.
So I'm here to jump in head
first. and hopefully we can
find love in the midst of
all the chaos.
Like Kat and Patrick from
'10 Things I Hate About You.'
You know the movie?
Oh. this is literally not a rom-com.
I'm not feeling like
that's my husband.
OK. now for
the ring exchange.
So who has the rings?
I do.
Oh. you have the rings.
Wonderful.
On paper. seems exactly as it
should be with his attributes
and his characteristics.
And. you know. his values.
But I just can't get past that
he forgot the rings.
God. I hate thinking about it.
Oh!
So it is with profound joy
that I now get to pronounce you
as husband and wife.
You may share your
first married kiss.
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
So far. this doesn't feel
like the fairy tale
I pictured for myself.
This feels like something out of.
I don't know.
some sort of comedy movie.
but it's not romantic comedy.
It's just comedy with.
like. Adam Sandler.
And I don't like it.
I just don't feel like
I got my fairy tale.
I don't feel like Meg Ryan
in 'You've Got Mail.'
Next. Gia's big day.
Hey. she's diva-ing.
You come in here
with this (BLEEP) energy.
It's too much.
Does she think that this
is the first bridezilla
I've ever had to deal with?
I don't want you
in the limo. (BLEEP) off.
With one couple married.
we reveal our second pairing.
As we meet one of the most
hard-working
and ambitious grooms to date.
I live life in the fast lane.
I don't know where
the turn off button is.
apart from when I lie down.
I'm very disciplined.
I'm very driven. I get up at four.
I go to bed at eight.
I don't drink. I don't smoke.
It was never an option for me
to live an ordinary life.
I just want an exceptional life.
And that's what I'm
working towards.
I'm Scott. I'm 33
and I'm a business owner
from the Gold Coast.
I own three businesses.
I own a finance brokerage.
a jet ski mechanic repair shop.
and I sell cars at a car dealership.
I'll start from the 4 a.m. wakeups
seven days a week. I'm up.
I'm out the door.
I'm at the gym.
and I'm in my office before 6 a.m.
and I'll work till
the sun goes down.
I'm married to my business.
I love it.
That's like my wife
at the moment.
I think the ambition comes
from my grandfather.
who worked so hard.
He set up the family
in a successful way.
meaning they're going
to be fine forever.
I want to take on that job now.
I want to be the next person
that looks after my family.
How do you see love and a partner
and a marriage
fitting into this life
that you have built for
yourself that's so structured?
Well. that's what's
super hard. obviously.
And that's what I'm here for.
to compromise and make time.
It's very hard to do so.
but I'm willing to
compromise. put it that way.
So it's hard to answer
at this moment.
because I just have to put myself
in the deep end
and see what the experiment
gives me.
So what would it mean for you
to find love in this experiment?
It would mean a lot because
I find that's literally.
I've built this career
and success and this health.
And. you know. I'm so happy
with myself
and I know there's something
missing.
And it's. you know.
my person.
I want to share
life with someone.
So it means so much to me.
I just really. I really want it.
I picture this perfect life
that my parents have given to
me and my brothers. and I want
to carry that as well.
My parents are so happy.
they're beautiful. and I want that.
You're going to have to
compromise and make room
for somebody in your life.
That's why it's hard.
Yes. And she's got to be
as good as your mother.
100%.
It's not all about work.
I'm definitely working
very hard.
not only for myself
but for my woman.
I want to share a luxury life
with someone.
My perfect type of woman.
someone who looks after themselves
as much as I do.
You know. presents themself well.
Beautiful eyes. beautiful body.
I want a hot girl. 100%.
I was in my past relationship.
yeah.
Um. we just weren't
having any sex.
I was waking up with wet dreams
every day.
I'm in my 30s.
Like. I need to have sex.
I have a massive high sex drive.
Sex is really important. I didn't
have it in my last relationship.
Sex wasn't important to him.
I do have a high sex drive.
I'm looking for a man who can.
who can match me in every way.
but sexually.
that he's a bit explorative.
I don't want vanilla.
I know my worth.
I've never been cheated on
because I'm a catch.
I cook. I clean. I have a brain.
I'll keep him stimulated.
And I'm up at 6 a.m.
looking like a Barbie. that's it.
My name's Gia. I'm 35
and I'm a disability support
worker from Melbourne.
I think people perceive me
as just a bimbo.
given how I look and everything.
But beneath the fake lips.
fake teeth.
fake tits. is the realest girl.
And there's so much
more to me than that.
I'm a mum.
I have a little daughter.
She's the most amazing.
kind girl.
It's a girls' night.
Yay!
Hm.
Um...
Oh. shit.
She's like the love of my life.
I put everything into
being a mum. Everything.
She's my reason for living.
I'm so proud that
she is who she is.
I think it's important
that she's confident. as much as me.
And as a mother. I want to show her
that it's OK to be herself and never
let sombody dull your shine.
Why is that so important to you.
to show her that?
I was very bullied in school.
Very. very bullied.
And it went all the way
through high school. Really?
Yep.
What were they targeting?
Boys would say things like.
"Why don't you grow some tits.
surfboard."
And. like. "Have you ever had
a boyfriend?"
And obviously. I didn't.
I never dated boys.
didn't have a boyfriend
'til I was. like. 20.
I didn't really
have many friends.
I didn't fit in with the other
girls. I didn't fit in.
I was kind of a weird loner.
so I feel like
it shaped me to be who I am.
I want him to just
like me. for me.
I want my future husband to be
manly. like an alpha male leader
type of guy who I can trust.
I like people with ambition.
who have drive.
Who's a really hard working
guy with some goals.
I'm not here to live ordinary.
I want to be remembered.
I want my future husband
to stand out.
I want a manly man.
please.
You know there's more to Gia
than meets the eye.
She's a big personality.
But make no mistake.
there is a lot of
vulnerability about her.
She has a huge heart.
She's a dedicated mother.
And now she's really focused
on finding a really positive
role model for her daughter.
Well. one thing remains.
Will Scott be willing to take
on Gia and her daughter?
We know he wants a family.
but does he want it right now?
One thing about Gia and Scott
is that they both faced
relationship breakdowns because of
the lack of sexual chemistry
in a relationship. and that
is something that they both
place very high on their
priority list.
But I truly believe
they will bring the heat
to the experiment.
These two have the potential
for the highest level of
sexual chemistry we've ever seen
on Married at First Sight.
So I say. let's lock 'em in.
The next couple have been matched -
Gia and Scott.
It's the highly anticipated
morning of Gia and Scott's wedding.
and the nervous bride to be
is trying to remain calm
as the clock ticks ever closer
to her big moment.
It's getting there.
We've got to do the hair.
It's just a time crunch
and it's stressful.
And to help soothe the single
mum's wedding day jitters.
Gia has called on two of her closest
friends. Will and Brooke.
to help bring some calm.
(EXCITED GREETINGS)
Where are you?
OK.
All right.
Champagne.
Glasses.
They're very. um...
I feel like they've had drinks
before they came here.
They've lit eyes.
Gia! Why is she quiet?
Three. idiot!
I only have two hands. bitch!
Ah!
(LAUGHTER)
Like. they are full-on already
at this time of the morning.
Like. it's too much.
Woo!
Here we go.
It's not about them.
It's not Brooke and Will show today.
It's not.
Give me a minute. You know?
We're the ultimate
hype girls.
We are here to make
everything smooth sailing.
Let's go!
Gia!
Where is she?
Babe!
Bring the energy.
Bring the vibes.
Make her feel comfortable.
(LAUGHTER)
Make her excited for this.
Gia! That's why we were selected.
Mm.
Why is there so many stairs?
OK. one more.
Wait. are you sure?
Let's just try it.
Not yet. Not yet.
Oh. I hear her!
Babe!
No. no. Not yet! Not yet!
We're here. hi!
Wait. not yet. Not yet!
I'm not ready yet. guys.
Like. (BLEEP) off.
Are you kidding me?
No. Don't. don't speak to me
like that. Sorry.
We have a shit-tonne
still to do.
Don't distract me. like.
we're really time crunch.
Breathe. Don't piss me off.
Breathe.
No. breath! Calm down!
It's my wedding.
Don't be a bridezilla.
I was good till you guys came.
I'm not even lying.
Can you guys just.
like. (BLEEP) off for five?
She is being
an absolute diva.
You're pissing me off.
Seriously.
Oh. here we go.
You (BLEEP) drama queen!
Horrible! Absolutely horrible!
It's fine.
OK. she's diva-ing.
You come in here with this energy.
it's too much.
Babe. calm down.
It's my (BLEEP) wedding.
Reign it in.
No. Uh-uh.
Not OK.
I'm not that bitch. honey.
I can't deal with it. I don't want
you in the limo. I'm done.
(BLEEP) off.
Yep. fine.
Yeah. you're too...
He's too much this morning.
Bitch!
Psycho.
I'm pissed off.
She's being ridiculous.
She's absolutely
being ridiculous.
Oh my god.
Like. we're at a time crunch.
They're already drunk.
It's. it's like they need
to chill it out.
Like. they're giving me anxiety.
Don't pick your best friend
out of ten years!
Don't treat me like
I'm a piece of shit!
That's absolutely bullshit!
I totally get it.
But does she think
this is my first rodeo?
Does she think that this is
the first bridezilla
I've ever had to deal with?
Hello! Hello!
Um...
Is she all right?
Shut up! Shut up!
Jesus!
If I did. they need to
get the (BLEEP) over it.
it's my wedding. not theirs.
Chill out. diva.
Like...
Like. you're not Mariah Carey.
Sit down.
Like. it's my wedding.
Shut up.
How can I help?
How can I calm you down?
Pacing.
I just need to just...
Get it out.
Energy. Energy.
It's just so unfair.
Do you need a cheeseburger?
No. I'm on a diet.
Having arrived late
to their ceremony.
after forgetting the rings.
and chewing gum
throughout the vows.
Mel isn't feeling
particularly enamoured
with her new husband. Luke.
and the tension is palpable.
How are you feeling?
I feel like I am in
the doghouse a little bit.
It shouldn't be like that.
should it?
The last thing I wanted
to do was. like.
make my future wife. now my wife.
upset on her wedding day.
Um. and that's exactly
what I did.
Which is really sad
for me to hear.
Yeah. true.
I feel like it is a bit
of a wake-up call.
Like. to me.
just to be super mindful
not to let her down again.
So I'm going to do my best
to try and make her feel
better about the situation
at least.
That's not how weddings
are supposed to go.
Like. obviously I'm supposed
to be there first.
but like. I don't wanna say
any buts.
Yeah. I'll just say I'm sorry.
Yeah. I feel like I've got
a little bit of redeeming to do.
Congratulations on your
beautiful fairy tale wedding.
Mm. Can I get you guys at
the end here for me? Yep.
It's your redemption arc.
Try harder. Luke!
No. this is where it starts.
I mean.
He hasn't redeemed himself yet.
You're looking at each other
for me there. Yeah.
(FORCED LAUGH)
My bar at the start
of the day was here.
(SIGHS)
But after the wedding.
it was here.
He's got that much to go.
Just keep holding it
for me.
I've just got a little
technical hiccup to sort out.
I hate this.
Beautiful day for a wedding.
Right. here we go.
Whoa.
Should have taken the shoes off
and walked barefoot.
Wow. what a beautiful beach.
Nice to meet you.
Hey.
Fancy seeing you guys here.
Anticipation's killing me.
As Gia and Scott's
family and friends gather
at the venue. back at Gia's.
earlier this morning.
a catastrophic feud
erupted between her
and her Man of Honour.
Will.
And since then.
things have taken another turn.
(LAUGHTER)
Oh!
I love you.
I love you too!
But don't be. don't be
a drama queen today.
I love you so much. but don't.
OK.
Just be my. be my calm today.
Sorry. Of course!
I didn't really read the room.
And it's like. like I said...
It's over. It's done.
I've known her
for over ten years.
Yeah.
It's fine. It's fine.
We yell. we scream.
we move on.
Mole.
You (BLEEP).
Slut. You bitch!
You're a bitch.
Love you.
OK. The war is over.
Oh my god!
My parent's marriage is
definitely my form of standard.
They've been married
for just under 40 years
and I want to carry that legacy.
Marrying a complete stranger
is pushing yourself
out of your comfort zone
for anyone.
Not knowing who she is.
what she looks like.
It's a big gamble for me.
But I'm all about risks.
It could go one way or the other.
but I'm ready
to take the next step.
I'm just ready to turn around
and see my beautiful bride.
Oh. here he comes.
Hello.
Yes. Scotty!
Hey. guys.
How're you going?
I'm Scott. Nice to meet you.
How you goin'. mate?
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
How you feeling. Scott?
I feel good.
Yeah?
Are you guys prepared for this?
No.
Not really. no.
Are you?
Well. not really. but I'll do
my best to take care of her.
Do you know what
you're expecting?
I don't know what I'm expecting.
We're at a (BLEEP) beach!
Breathe. breathe.
Guys. I'm at a (BLEEP) beach
in my heels. Are you joking?
Babe. you can't...
Are you joking?
You can't control it.
I'm getting a god damn sand wedding
with my $1.500 shoes.
I'm a bougie bitch!
I'm trying not to laugh because
I don't want you to punch me.
Guys. how am I gonna
wear these heels?
I'm holding out hope.
I don't really know
what to tell you. babe.
We love you.
Bye. babies. Bye. I love you.
See you there!
Love you.
Oh my god. oh my god.
oh my god.
He's tall.
Yeah. He's tall!
Hello.
Hi!
WILL: Oh my god. are you nervous?
I feel pretty good.
Thank god!
Thank you. Jesus!
Um. first of all...
BOTH: Hot.
What's your name?
Scott.
Strong name.
Nice to meet you guys.
BOTH: Scotty is a hottie.
Ten out of ten.
Wow.
Smash!
I think Will likes him.
If she runs. I'm up.
Do you want me to give you
a little bit of reassurance?
Please do.
She's gonna like you.
Will I love her?
Yeah.
Strap in. buddy.
PRODUCER: We're ready?
(BLEEP) all right. let's do it.
I would love nothing more
than to just have a man
for me and for my daughter.
That we had a consistent.
stable man in our life
that was good for us.
It'd mean everything.
I want him to be a good man.
I know I'm a lot. and I will
keep him on his toes.
I'm not easy. but I'm worth it.
I am a little bit outspoken.
a little bit fiery.
Some people might not like that.
But this is who I am.
(BLEEP)!
Beach! WILL: I know!
The (BLEEP)? WILL: I know!
(BLEEP) (BLEEP)!
WILL: I said... You right?
No. You just hear her
from a mile away.
I literally have
to take these off.
I'm gonna have to help you.
Hang on.
I'm taking them off.
Take 'em off.
Take these off.
(BLEEP) I can't.
(BLEEP)!
Scotty typically doesn't
like girls that swear a lot.
(BLEEP)! Are you ready?
You shitting yourself?
I know he finds it an ick.
He looks good looking
from behind the veil.
Can you hold it as
I'm walking?
I can't even look cute.
Yeah.
(BLEEP).
Give me your hand.
(BLEEP) (BLEEP).
Right?
Hold my hand. sweetie.
Hold the veil.
Oh my god!
(BLEEP)!
Can you hold it as I'm walking?
'Cause I can't even look cute.
Yeah.
(BLEEP).
Hold my hand. sweetie.
Hold the veil.
I've got the veil.
Oh my god. oh my god.
Oh my god.
(BLEEP).
Oh! Shit.
I had to take my shoes off.
I couldn't walk.
OK. Oh my god.
Hi! Hello!
Hello.
The moment I turned around
and saw her.
I was speechless.
She's definitely
a beautiful girl.
Wow. you look good.
Oh! Shit. oh my God.
Pretty happy. I'm stoked.
How are you?
I'm Scott.
I'm Gia. Oh. do we hug?
What do we do?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Scott. Nice to meet you.
You're cute.
What a gorgeous couple!
I know!
He's hot. Come on now. He is.
Yeah. definitely.
Make beautiful babies.
From a mum's perspective. Yeah.
No. very cute.
I'm happy. So we're good.
Are you happy?
I think you're stunning.
So. yeah.
Oh my god!
Yeah. I'm definitely physically
attracted to him.
Good now. You're good.
I'm good. I'm good. I'm good.
He has nice teeth
and I'm a teeth person.
So the first thing was
like. OK. nice smile.
He has nice eyes too.
No. but neither are mine.
I think we both.
we've got matching veneers.
so I think it's meant to be.
Welcome. We gather to celebrate
one of life's
most beautiful milestones.
The union of Gia and Scott
in marriage.
Surrounded by your
family and friends.
I invite you to reaffirm
your commitment to one another.
I bet I'm first.
I hope you're first.
Great.
Where's my seat belt?
Yeah.
So. hi. I'm Gia.
If you're thinking I look good
on the outside. which.
let's face it. you are...
Just wait until you
get to know my heart.
I've got a lot of love to give.
a loud laugh and a mouth that
sometimes gets me into trouble.
I'm confident
and often unhinged.
But always a damn good time.
Let's get one thing straight.
I'm the whole package.
I'll cook better
than your mother.
Ooh!
Jesus!
Make you laugh better
than your best mates.
And look hot doing it.
But love hasn't always
been kind to me.
I've walked into rooms
and felt judged
before I've even said a word.
And I know what it's
like to be misunderstood
and looked at and not seen.
Because underneath these
perfect fake tits...
..is a girl with real substance.
I like tits. That's all right.
I might look plastic.
but I promise you.
everything else about me is real.
So if you're ready for fireworks.
a few challenges.
and the kind of love that
doesn't come easy but is worth
every second. then I'm all
the way in. if you are too.
I am too.
Yay!
She sounds perfect.
From what I heard
and what I saw.
I think she looks like
a very exciting person.
This is crazy.
And I think she's going to spark up
Scott's life in a good way.
because I think sometimes.
he can be a little boring.
Yeah. So. yeah. it'll be good.
I think. um.
Gia is what Scott needs.
Yes.
Totally agree.
I actually feel like they've
tried to pair them up perfectly.
Like. she's a match.
I feel there's a spark.
There's definitely a good.
genuine connection there.
I think she is definitely
the type of woman
to keep me on my toes.
Got a very strong personality.
very up front.
I like that. I'm very invested
in to getting to know Gia
and learning about each other
and seeing where it takes us.
(LOUDLY CLEARS THROAT)
Hi. I'm Scott. as you're aware.
I'm a business owner.
an early riser. a guy who lives
life fast and full.
Today. I stand here not just
as a guy who's achieved a lot.
but a man who is ready
to give even more.
I'm a man of routine
and structure.
I'm up at 4 a.m. to train.
Like me! I eat clean.
I live a pretty
disciplined life.
But underneath all this
is someone who values softness
just as much as strength.
I'm looking for a connection
that makes me
feel safe to slow down.
Someone who can bring
a little calm to the chaos.
Marriage to me... Now I'm starting
to get nervous! I don't know why.
You're fine.
My legs started shaking and then
I don't know why I got nervous.
Maybe because I was super
attracted to her and. you know.
the nerves started coming out.
I think it's a good sign.
It means I'm genuinely interested.
WILL: He's really genuine.
He's really genuine.
I'm getting a very good vibe.
Yeah.
So here I am. fresh fade.
moisturised.
with all open heart. clear mind.
Let's write a real story - messy.
magic. honest. and completely ours.
Yay!
That was great.
I was starting to get nervous.
No. you're good.
No. we loved it.
Great.
Yeah.
I hope so.
I like him. I like the things
he said and what he's about.
I got a little bit more of
a glimpse into him
and. like. yeah. I like it.
That's not going to come off!
Good. Oh. good.
I've got big hands.
You know what big hands mean?
I feel good about
the match so far.
I feel like they've
gotten it good.
They're on point.
And now. family and friends.
I joyfully pronounce
Gia and Scott as husband and wife!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
You may now share
your first kiss!
(APPLAUSE)
She already told me she would
not kiss him. She kissed him.
So that to me says a lot
because she's very reserved.
even though she doesn't look it.
So. yeah. there's definitely
a spark.
You have to grab
my shoes up there.
You're my husband now.
Oh. here we go.
I'm gonna put them on.
I haven't liked anyone
in a really long time.
so...I'm really happy.
WILL: Can we get a big round of
applause for the newlyweds?
Gia and Scott!
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
Oh my gosh.
it's so cute in here.
Isn't it gorge?
Yes!
How are you feeling actually?
I'm stoked. hey.
Yeah?
Are you having fun?
Yeah. so good.
Gia. you have a husband.
I know. he's so cute too.
And you're just giggling
like a little school girl.
And I never do.
I never see her like this.
Oh. I like that.
Things are going too well.
and I'm just stressed
about telling him
I have a daughter.
Because if he's someone
who isn't a child person.
it might put him off.
I definitely know I want to tell him
at the end of the night.
I don't want to tell him when
we're just getting to know each
other.
It could be a red flag
for him and then he doesn't.
he writes me off.
So I'm gonna wait 'til later on
in the evening
when I think I've got a better
gauge on him.
Oh my god. I hope
no-one says anything.
Woo!
That's. like. my secret to tell.
I'll be really pissed.
That's so my secret to tell.
And they all know that. If anyone
in my wedding party does.
I'll literally kick 'em out.
So...yeah.
You can bombard me
with any question.
I'll answer. I'm very honest.
He's good under pressure.
I know Will
has a big question.
Do you have any children?
Wow.
After a delayed groom and an
uncomfortable photo shoot.
the vibe at Mel and Luke's
reception is painfully awkward.
and despite Luke's attempts to
apologise for his tardiness.
Mel remains distant.
We definitely could
have parked a minibus
between the both of us.
And the couple's cold body language
hasn't gone unnoticed
by the wedding guests.
They seem to be
sitting very far apart.
I was just thinking that.
Yeah. Mel is tilted a bit...
Away.
Yeah. She is reserved.
Yeah.
I feel like when he's talking to me.
I'm leaning backwards.
He hasn't redeemed himself
for being late to the wedding.
so I didn't feel like
I wanted to move closer.
I've got three sisters.
Have I told you that? Yeah.
We got Mum. Sophie. got Steph...
Hey. Mel!
And Liv.
Do you want to have
a chat to them?
Maybe in a little bit.
Nice. nice.
I mean. who's... She's not doing
much talking...
Mel definitely had
her guard up. I felt.
She wasn't giving as much
as what Luke was giving.
I like anything
just pretty active.
That's kind of why
I work on the farm.
I like being active. So like.
you know. going on boats
and all that kind of stuff.
Yeah.
I just felt like she
was a lot more serious.
a lot more conservative.
a lot more reserved.
I'm trying as hard as I can
with the conversations.
and I haven't really got too
much back.
I feel like she's been a bit quiet.
so I really want to
focus on getting to know her
as much as possible.
I want to show her that I care.
You've got goosebumps.
Let me give you this.
See. chivalry.
I know for Mel.
that that's really
important to her. Like.
that would speak massive volumes.
Yeah. true.
Yeah.
I agree.
I really like him.
Like. he opened a chair for her.
Like. he did all this stuff.
Like. I like. I know he was late.
but who cares?
I think he's really nice.
I'm just gonna go
talk to my mum.
See you in a bit.
Hey. Mummy.
Hey. darlin'.
I could see how hurt my
daughter was. obviously.
And she genuinely
was very. very upset.
What she could see
and what we could see
were a little bit different.
And I wanted her to have.
maybe have an understanding
that there's always two sides
to every story. right?
He seems like a nice person.
His family seem lovely.
Is she kind of like
your usual type that
you would go for?
I'd say she's my type.
Great!
Yeah.
When you kind of look at the bigger
picture. you're going.
OK. he was a little bit late.
Things happen and you can't
really judge a person
on one little action.
We all thought he was a lovely.
lovely person.
so hopefully she'll move on
pretty quickly from this.
Love you.
Love you more.
As Mel's mum persuades her
to move past the ring debacle.
over at Gia and Scott's wedding.
Gia's man of honour. Will.
has just brought up the one topic
of conversation
that she specifically
asked her guests to avoid
around her new husband.
Do you have any children?
Wow! I told everyone
not to say anything.
What's he thinking.
bringing up the kid question?
No. I don't.
No. you don't?
I don't need my
man of honour
prompting conversations like that.
Because. like.
he could start to ask me
those sort of questions back.
And I'm just not ready yet
for that.
Narrowly missing a bullet.
Gia tries to relax into
the reception as the rest of
her guests find ways to bond
with their new in-laws.
Be there for her
and she'll be there for you.
You know what I mean?
I'm a Cancer.
I'm always there for my person.
Oh my god. darling. so am I!
Ah. Gia!
Oh. look. I think as far
as his family and I go.
we all love each other.
We all seem to get along
really. really well.
Oh. look. this is lovely.
I really love them all.
Couldn't have asked for better.
Wow.
Absolutely love
everybody in the room.
I think they're very genuine people.
It was great.
Uncle? OK.
So what does Gia do?
Gia does...
She's a house mum.
She looks after her daughter.
Oh. OK. she's got a daughter?
Yeah.
Oh. OK. Yeah.
Yeah. yeah.
I (BLEEP) up.
Big time.
Oh. shit. What have I done?
So what does Gia do?
Gia does...
She's...a house mum.
She looks after her daughter.
Oh. OK. she's got a daughter.
Yeah.
Oh. OK. Yeah.
Yeah. yeah.
I (BLEEP) up bad.
Anyway. good to meet you.
Yes. you too.
You too. we'll catch up.
I got a bit carried away
and I accidentally
spilled the beans and said
about Gia's daughter.
I wasn't supposed to say that.
Get out!
So. they actually listened
to everything.
like. when we were talking.
I just wanted to say hello.
Welcome to our family.
You're gorgeous.
I think you're going
to be perfect.
I love your dress.
You're gorgeous.
You accept me so far? I'm OK?
Yes!
You're perfect.
You just...
What you've said and vows
and everything.
I thought. 'Oh. wow. yeah.'
Guys. like.
I love this family.
What?
How the hell does she know that?
Oh my god. you found out?
That's a big one.
Who the hell told him
I had a kid?
I told everyone not to
say anything. so I'm kind of
blindsided by my own family
at this point.
Who said it?
Because I'm pissed off.
Who'd you hear that from?
It was John.
Johnny!
Who? Did you tell her dad
she's got a daughter?
You're not supposed to say!
I know. I slipped.
Oh!
Great! John. my darling cousin.
He can't help himself.
He's got a big mouth.
He just blurts stuff out.
It's all his fault.
He'll cop it from his wife tonight.
don't worry.
Gia. Gia.
So it wasn't me.
It was your uncle.
GIA: John has (BLEEP) this.
And it's just.
it's just set me off.
Like. everything was great
until this point.
And I feel like Scott could back off
because of this now.
Like. it was my secret to tell.
Uncle John should be scared
because I'm coming for him now.
like. I'm pissed.
What'd you do?
I think I've made a mistake.
I wasn't supposed to...
You have!
I know.
It's so my secret to tell.
Do you know how heartbreaking
that was?
I'm trying to make the family
accept me. like...
I know. Gia. I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it!
It just came out.
I'm trying to make them accept me.
And then the mum comes over.
"Oh. you got a kid?"
I'm like. what?
I'm really sorry.
It was just...
I didn't mean it...
I wanted to pull him aside in a way
that. like. made him understand it
a bit. like...
Gia. please. I didn't mean it.
It just came out.
But Scotty doesn't know.
He doesn't have a kid.
so. like. what if he's like.
'Oh. I can't accept that.'
you know? And I like him.
He likes you.
Do you think he likes me
enough to accept that? Yes.
OK. I'm really sorry.
Can you accept my apology?
Yeah.
You didn't mean it.
You didn't...
I'm excited that I'm here.
I'm happy you invited me.
and I didn't mean it. OK.
Come here. come here. darling.
I love you. OK? Yep.
I'm sorry. I really am.
If he doesn't know now.
someone else is going to say it.
And I'm. like. freaking out.
Like. I gotta tell him.
Can I pull you for a sec
for a chat? Cool.
We've started off good.
and this could change things.
When I tell him this information.
like. he might be
really put off and be like.
'Oh. I don't know if I like
her now.'
Are you asking me something?
No. I have to tell you something.
Shit.
Don't worry about it.
I'm here for you.
Don't worry.
You right?
Yep.
It's all good.
OK.
It's all right.
All right.
Did you hear things?
Did I hear things?
What things?
Around the room. Like. we were
talking about something.
No.
Someone said something.
and it's like
something that I wanted to tell you
myself. And I feel like...
I mustn't have been listening.
Um...
Like. I have a kid.
You have a kid?
After an intervention
from her mum
to convince her to forgive Luke
for being late to the wedding.
and after multiple apologies
from Luke himself.
the question is. is Mel
finally ready to move past it?
Um...
Well. obviously. like.
I won't lie to you.
I feel like.
like. you were so late.
Yeah.
And then you came
and you were chewing gum.
Yeah. Yeah. yeah. yeah.
Well. like...
I feel like it's going
to take me a little while
to get past that.
I thought she had forgiven me
for being late to the wedding
a while ago. but then she
brought it up again.
So I feel like there's still
something that's there. Um...
Yeah. I mean. I really am
sorry for coming late.
and I just want you to know that's.
that's not really me.
And. like. maybe you don't
believe that yet. but...
Like. I want to show you
that I'm not actually like that.
Yeah.
Yeah. I think it might still be
a bit of. a bit of
an ongoing thing for a little bit.
No doubt. I slipped up
a couple of times.
But I would like to just
move forward with it
and not keep looking at it.
kind of thing.
Mm.
Yeah. I'm not sure what
he's expecting from me
after today's played out.
I think that he expects me
just to push it
under the rug and let it go.
Yeah. I'm keen to just like.
yeah. show you that that's not
actually me and. like.
move forward with it all.
Like. I feel like
I was just upset
that it's tainted my experience.
Yeah.
You know. you kind of lose sleep
over something like this.
Yeah. Fair enough.
Mm.
Yeah.
After her uncle accidentally
exposed her secret.
Gia has been forced to reveal
she's a mum.
and has been worried about
how Scott will react.
I have a kid.
You have a kid?
That's fine.
Is that all right?
Like. I don't know.
Like... I've been with someone
with a kid before.
Oh. you have?
Yeah. 100%.
Oh. OK.
Is that a deal breaker?
I loved them to death.
No. 100% it's not.
It's not.
As long as you're a good mum.
The best mum...
That's all that matters.
Like. that's my favourite thing.
And it was like when you
asked me questions about me.
I so badly wanted to be like...
You just want to tell me.
Yeah. and I can't. I've been. like.
hiding it. And it's like...
You just gotta let it out.
Well. you don't have a kid.
And I'm like.
you could be. like...
Against them. No. I love
my brother's kids so much.
Like. I'm. like. the favourite
uncle. I love the kids.
There's nothing wrong with that.
Yeah.
You're good.
You can breathe now.
(BLEEP). Does it feel like a weight
off your shoulder?
Yes! How do you feel about being.
like. a stepdad? Potentially.
As long as they like me too.
To be honest.
I don't think about it.
like. she's a part of you.
which is a part of me.
I'm so relieved.
Everything I've said
that I'm like.
could potentially put him off.
he's like. "I love that.
I'm fine with this."
I'm like. what?
I'm going to be FaceTiming her.
saying goodnight
and shit. And I'm like...
I'll jump on the phone.
Will you? Yeah. 100%.
OK.
I can feel for her.
You know. being a single mum.
it would be very hard.
A lot of guys would say.
"Nah. it's a deal breaker"
and I'm willing to take on the role
of being a stepfather.
We're OK?
Yeah. yeah. You're fine.
Honestly. I couldn't thank
the experts enough
for matching me with someone like
Gia.
To the dancefloor.
as your first dance
as husband and wife.
BOTH: # That's the way it's gonna be
little darling... #
This is the woman.
This is the one
I've been looking for.
I'll do it with my teeth.
(CHEERS)
This is a true love story
right now.
I've got sore cheeks
from smiling.
I could see myself
falling for him.
I mean. it's so early.
but I've just...
The spark I've had. I haven't
had butterflies or a spark
like that. literally. in years.
I just feel so safe.
And I feel like I can tackle
whatever's ahead.
the next three months with him.
Captioned by AI-Media
ai-media.tv
Tomorrow night. it's Bec's turn
to walk down the aisle.
(RIPPING NOISE)
Oh!
Oh my god!
In one of the most
unpredictable weddings...
(ALL EXCLAIM)
..the experiment's ever seen.
Oh my god.
Just want something serious.
I don't want to be with anyone
that gets arrested.
And...
Chris may be our greatest
sceptic of all.
This opinionated groom...
..is the experiment's
biggest cynic.
Let's try and be the 0.00001%
that works from this experiment.
But will he be proven
wrong by the experts?
I don't care. I don't care.
I don't care.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm